const STORE = [
    {
        question: 'Which one is the most balanced workout plan?' ,
        answers: [
            'running, weight lifting, yoga',
            'running, biking, swiming',
            'biking, weight lifting, swiming',
            'yoga, pilate, swiming'
        ],
        correctAnswer:'running, weight lifting, yoga'
    },
    {
        question: 'Which one is the toughest workout?' ,
        answers: [
            'walking',
            'running',
            'shopping',
            'sprinting'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'sprinting'
    },
    {
        question: 'What target heart rate should you aim for during cardio?' ,
        answers: [
            'twice your resting heart rate' ,
            'three times your resting heart rate' ,
            '50 to 80% of max heart rate' ,
            'resting hear rate'
        ],
        correctAnswer: '50 to 80% of max heart rate'
    },
    {
        question: 'what muscle group does squat workout?' ,
        answers: [
            'quads' ,
            'back' ,
            'biceps' ,
            'forearms'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'quads'
    },
    {
        question: 'what muscle group does pull ups workout?' ,
        answers: [
            'back' ,
            'hamstrings' ,
            'butt',
            'quads'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'back'
    },
    {
        question: 'what is a superset?' ,
        answers: [
            "super man's set" ,
            'quads workout' ,
            'pull ups' ,
            'hiit exercise of strength training'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'hiit exercise of strength training'
    },
    {
        question: 'how many days a week is best for strength training?' ,
        answers: [
            '7 days' ,
            '0 days' ,
            '5 days in a row' ,
            '3-4 days a week with days in between for rest'
        ],
        correctAnswer: '3-4 days a week with days in between for rest'
    },
    {
        question: 'why do you rest between strength training?' ,
        answers: [
            "don't want to work out" ,
            "ate too much can't workout" ,
            'need rest to build muscle' ,
            "don't want to sweat"
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'need rest to build muscle'
    },
    {
        question: 'what is bodyweight trainging good for?',
        answers: [
            'models' ,
            'better motivation' ,
            'eating food after' ,
            'no access to the gym or equipment'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'no access to the gym or equipment'
    },
    {
        question: 'what not to eat before workout?' ,
        answers: [
            'fish' ,
            'hard-boiled egg' ,
            'cookie' ,
            'protein shake'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'cookie'
    }
];